<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HeroLFG</title>
    <link>https://herolfg.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on HeroLFG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 06:23:08 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://herolfg.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Minerval Arts</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/minerval-arts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/minerval-arts/</guid>
      <description>I would pay money to see good conversations happening because good conversations are absent in our world. I believe other people would also be interested in paying money to see good conversations happening. Gandhi taught to be the change you wish to see and my goal is to create a place where good conversations happen.
I have created a Patreon account which allows subscribers to gain attention on my Discord server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Failing Justice Systems</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/failing-justice-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/failing-justice-systems/</guid>
      <description>I have always felt repulsed by rules which cause harm to people who are not causing harm. I think everyone should feel safe in a world where I carefully and illegally drive through an intersection when the light is red. There is no reason for the traffic camera to be used to mail me a ticket which could culminate in a shooting between myself and a law enforcer because I am unwilling to cooperate with a justice system which causes harm to good people disobeying bad laws.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing Humans</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/managing-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/managing-humans/</guid>
      <description>I have completed the first part of Managing Humans by Michael Lopp. I think the most interesting chapter in the book is titled &amp;ldquo;Titles are Toxic&amp;rdquo;. Lopp suggests titles are toxic because they attempt to place value on humans who are beautiful snowflakes. He thinks titles are as useless as business cards and resumes. And I tend to agree with his sentiment.
A general problem I see in organizations is that people keep their role if they are “good enough”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disagreement with Eric Weinstein and Peter Thiel</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/disagreement-with-eric-weinstein-and-peter-thiel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/disagreement-with-eric-weinstein-and-peter-thiel/</guid>
      <description>How do people with good ideas and without power teach people with power who could best help make the ideas into our reality when there is no obvious way to even begin the conversation? People with good ideas and motivations need to be able to see a gate which can be opened for them and the paths which lead to that gate. What I have been trying to do is imagine gates and paths by which I am able to reach, teach, and learn with other people who are willing and able to solve important problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Encounter Disagreement</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-encounter-disagreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-encounter-disagreement/</guid>
      <description>I am writing this with Eric Weinstein in mind. But this general approach to learning and cooperating with a large community can be implemented by anyone who has a sufficiently large following. I am excited to see people trying to figure out how to improve the sense making organ for a large community of people.
You have realized that you need to put forth some effort having conversations with new people who have new ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ending the War on Drugs</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/ending-the-war-on-drugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/ending-the-war-on-drugs/</guid>
      <description>Why was the War on Drugs started? If I steelman the arguments for the idea of controlling substances, I would imagine a different time without the internet when people had access to less information. I am young enough to remember researching cannabis and psilocybin on the internet before I experimented with those substances. There was a time when it was much harder to do your research in order to understand a substance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disagreement</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/disagreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 09:18:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/disagreement/</guid>
      <description>Facebook doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a thumbs down reaction. And even if it did have a thumbs down reaction that reaction could get lost in the noise of other reactions. A disagreement is potentially the most valuable signal of all because it is an opportunity for learning to take place.
When I share this post on the internet with you it is an invitation to a discussion so that learning may take place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Philosophy Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-philosophy-knowledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 06:18:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-philosophy-knowledge/</guid>
      <description>The value of work is related to all the costs and benefits of the work including the externalities. The usefulness of knowledge is based on its relationship with work. My economics knowledge has not been useful because I have never been in a position where my ignorance on the subject would be costly. My ability to obtain useful and valuable knowledge is dependent on my ability to recognize which kinds of knowledge are not useful to me at that point in time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Economics Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-economics-knowledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 06:18:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-economics-knowledge/</guid>
      <description>When I write about a world without hunger curi (Elliot Temple) wonders what I know about economics.
The Basics There is a supply of goods and services. There is demand for those goods and services. The prices of goods and services are related to supply and demand. If a good or service is scarce the price can be higher than when that same good or service is abundant assuming all other variables like demand are the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A World Without Hunger</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/a-world-without-hunger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/a-world-without-hunger/</guid>
      <description>The first person I have known to take autonomous agriculture technology seriously is Douglas Mallette, founder of Cybernated Farm Systems.
We can technically feed the world with autonomous agriculture technology which eventually requires no human labor.
It has been said that you can give a man a fish and feed him for a day. It has been said that you can teach a man to fish and feed him the rest of his life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Paths Forward Policy</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-paths-forward-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 07:18:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-paths-forward-policy/</guid>
      <description>The Paths Forward policy idea was developed by Elliot Temple.
You can see the history of updates for this post by using github version control.
My Policy I am willing to spend over 1 hour per day on average having public conversations with people on the internet. You can join my discord server, connect with me on linkedin, or connect with me on facebook. I plan on building a better discussion plugin for this site instead of disqus and recommend against using disqus for now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human Resource Problem</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/human-resource-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 09:18:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/human-resource-problem/</guid>
      <description>Humans have the potential to solve many big problems which are not currently being solved. For example, we could eventually be living in a world where malnutrition and starvation is avoidable. The main reason we live in a world where humans suffer from malnutrition is because humans have not figured out how to work together effectively. I have broadly called this general problem of humans not working together effectively &amp;ldquo;HRP&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telework Experience</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/telework-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 09:18:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/telework-experience/</guid>
      <description>When telework is done with the right tools and processes, it is far more efficient and effective than working on site.
Whether you are new to remote work or you have been doing it for years, I am confident that there is something we can do to reduce costs and increase the effectiveness of your organization through telework.
I have accumulated about 6 years of telework experience since graduating from Auburn University in 2008.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Connect with me on LinkedIn
Or join my Discord server</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>