<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HeroLFG</title>
    <link>https://herolfg.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on HeroLFG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 07:18:08 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://herolfg.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Paths Forward Policy</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-paths-forward-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 07:18:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-paths-forward-policy/</guid>
      <description>I am willing to spend over 1 hour per day on average having public conversations with people on the internet. You can join my discord server, connect with me on linkedin, or connect with me on facebook. I plan on building a better discussion plugin for this site instead of disqus and recommending against using disqus for now.
If you ask me a publicly visible question, I will eventually respond. I will usually respond within 48 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human Resource Problem</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/human-resource-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 09:18:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/human-resource-problem/</guid>
      <description>Humans have the potential to solve many big problems which are not currently being solved. For example, we could eventually be living in a world where malnutrition and starvation is avoidable. The main reason we live in a world where humans suffer from malnutrition is because humans have not figured out how to work together effectively. I have broadly called this general problem of humans not working together effectively &amp;ldquo;HRP&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telework Experience</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/telework-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 09:18:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/telework-experience/</guid>
      <description>When telework is done with the right tools and processes, it is far more efficient and effective than working on site.
Whether you are new to remote work or you have been doing it for years, I am confident that there is something we can do to reduce costs and increase the effectiveness of your organization through telework.
I have accumulated about 6 years of telework experience since graduating from Auburn University in 2008.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Connect with me on LinkedIn
Or email gavin @ herolfg.com</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>