<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>education on HeroLFG</title>
    <link>https://herolfg.com/tags/education/</link>
    <description>Recent content in education on HeroLFG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 06:23:08 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://herolfg.com/tags/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Failing Justice Systems</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/failing-justice-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/failing-justice-systems/</guid>
      <description>I have always felt repulsed by rules which cause harm to people who are not causing harm. I think everyone should feel safe in a world where I carefully and illegally drive through an intersection when the light is red. There is no reason for the traffic camera to be used to mail me a ticket which could culminate in a shooting between myself and a law enforcer because I am unwilling to cooperate with a justice system which causes harm to good people disobeying bad laws.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing Humans</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/managing-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/managing-humans/</guid>
      <description>I have completed the first part of Managing Humans by Michael Lopp. I think the most interesting chapter in the book is titled &amp;ldquo;Titles are Toxic&amp;rdquo;. Lopp suggests titles are toxic because they attempt to place value on humans who are beautiful snowflakes. He thinks titles are as useless as business cards and resumes. And I tend to agree with his sentiment.
A general problem I see in organizations is that people keep their role if they are “good enough”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disagreement with Eric Weinstein and Peter Thiel</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/disagreement-with-eric-weinstein-and-peter-thiel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/disagreement-with-eric-weinstein-and-peter-thiel/</guid>
      <description>How do people with good ideas and without power teach people with power who could best help make the ideas into our reality when there is no obvious way to even begin the conversation? People with good ideas and motivations need to be able to see a gate which can be opened for them and the paths which lead to that gate. What I have been trying to do is imagine gates and paths by which I am able to reach, teach, and learn with other people who are willing and able to solve important problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Encounter Disagreement</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-encounter-disagreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-encounter-disagreement/</guid>
      <description>I am writing this with Eric Weinstein in mind. But this general approach to learning and cooperating with a large community can be implemented by anyone who has a sufficiently large following. I am excited to see people trying to figure out how to improve the sense making organ for a large community of people.
You have realized that you need to put forth some effort having conversations with new people who have new ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>